let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "Which of the following sports facilities is not available at MAIT?",
    answer: "D) Swimming Pool",
    options: [
      "A) Basketball Court",
      "B) Tennis Court",
      "C) Cricket Ground",
      "D) Swimming Pool",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which university is MAIT affiliated with?",
    answer: "A) Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University (GGSIPU)",
    options: [
      "A) Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University (GGSIPU)",
      "B) Delhi Technological University (DTU)",
      "C) Jamia Millia Islamia (JMI)",
      "D) Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University (JNTU)",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which one of them is a cultural society of MAIT?",
    answer: "C) Literary Umbrella",
    options: ["A) IOSD", "B) GDSC", "C) Literary Umbrella", "D) IEEE"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question:
      "What year was Maharaja Agrasen Institute of Technology (MAIT) established?",
    answer: "B) 1999",
    options: ["A) 1997", "B) 1999", "C) 2001", "D) 2003"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which campus is MAIT located in?",
    answer: "B) Rohini",
    options: ["A) Dwarka", "B) Rohini", "C) Janakpuri", "D) Saket"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What does NSS stand for at MAIT?",
    answer: "A) National Service Scheme",
    options: [
      "A) National Service Scheme",
      "B) National Science Society",
      "C) National Student Society",
      "D) National Sports Society",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "Who is the founder of Maharaja Agrasen Institute of Technology (MAIT)?",
    answer: "C) Maharaja Agrasen Technical Education Society",
    options: [
      "A) Maharaja Agrasen",
      "B) Maharaja Surajmal",
      "C) Maharaja Agrasen Technical Education Society",
      "D) Maharaja Agrasen Hospital",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is not a course offered at MAIT?",
    answer: "D) Bioinformatics Engineering",
    options: [
      "A) Computer Science and Engineering",
      "B) Electronics and Communication Engineering",
      "C) Mechanical Engineering",
      "D) Bioinformatics Engineering",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question:
      "Which of the following is one of the technical societies at MAIT?",
    answer: "A) GDSC",
    options: ["A) GDSC", "B) Ayaam", "C) Affinity", "D) Funk in Motion"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the name of the annual technical fest at MAIT?",
    answer: "D) TnM-TechSurge n Mridang",
    options: [
      "A) Technotsav",
      "B) Innovision",
      "C) Technovision",
      "D) TnM-TechSurge n Mridang",
    ],
  },
];
